not a special human being,
but I don't want to see it.
The blue sky is bright, and
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it in a little bit.
Hai. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yolta, Ima!
Kyoumamaaakaaka!
Halanfancho konoomori!
Itsmoka so many tsukure!
Sanja karan, sigamae!
Kibi wo shinji te!
Mayoobu te, naayamu te!
Wanai naanara ikumou!
It's all coming together.
Tachibana's charm skill has proven useful.
I barely had to do anything.
So what exactly did you do to her?
I boosted the power of her charm skill.
Just enough to make it go a bit haywire,
which so happened to weaken the hero.
Two birds with one stone? By now,
the kingdom should be utterly overwhelmed
trying to quell the riots in the capital.
Providing us with the opportunity to
have the humans destroy themselves.
That is totally twisted!
Head made!
Emergency!
All communications with the troops
advancing on the capital have been cut off!
Are you saying they were wiped out?
Actually, it would seem they've all
gone back to their normal lives.
Our scouts say they're now
plowing fields completely naked.
Why naked?
That point remains unclear.
However, we can confirm that they've lost
all their memories of the last few days.
How could there be a skill that can instantly
dispel the heroes charms on hundreds?
It's impossible.
I don't get what the big deal is.
What do you think would happen if all our
charmed hostages made
an advance on the enemy,
only to have their charms dispelled
moments after they reached them?
Well, it'd make the hostages useless,
which would defeat the whole reason
why we're here in the first place.
Wait, that's really bad!
We can't take it!
No, this isn't happening.
All those peeled potatoes, mop floors,
and cobbled shoes can't be for nothing.
It took an entire year of working myself
to the bone just to become headmaid!
All the while patiently gathering information
so I could craft the perfect plan.
And yet somehow I miss
the one human in the
entire kingdom who can undo mind control?
Who even does that?
This is really bad!
This is really, really bad!
What are you gonna do?
This is really sad!
There's no use fighting it.
We'll abandon the kingdom
falls to charm strategy.
Oh, so does that mean you'll
have some kind of backup plan?
You know what?
Screw it, honestly.
How about we just blow
up the whole kingdom?
Hey, Iki, what is this place?
This chamber is where the kingdom
stores its strongest weapons.
Princess,
as much as I regret
that it's come to this,
due to unforeseen interference, we've
been forced to abandon our original plan.
The only path left to us
is to use our last resort.
Huh?
You're seeing one plan failed and now
we're already down to our last resort?
Sounds like it was a pretty
stupid plan to begin with.
I'd prefer, Your Highness, to see it as
a sign of how desperate our situation is.
Regardless, I'm not comfortable using the
Kingdom's defenses to achieve my own ends.
Yet you're fine with
half-measures, Your Highness.
You've borne the weight of
so much all by yourself.
The power behind that door is yours
to take by right, don't you think?
Remember that suffocating lonely world?
Do you truly miss your life in the castle?
But the seal...
It requires two royal family members.
There's no need to worry about that.
Let's not forget, you've also
been touched by the goddess.
Come on, you too, hero. Huh?
Oh, sorry, I haven't
really been listening.
Remember what I said?
You wanted to be stronger.
And I told you that I could
teach you a way to do that.
We have what we need.
So we can finally defeat Jinguji!
Jinguji
Manual, manual, manual.
Found it!
This doesn't feel right Why go so far?
The last thing I want to do
is threat military action.
Just to make a point to my father!
All this time.
And you still need it spelled out for you?
Working for you this last
year hasn't been excruciating.
That's why I'll save
her every second I spend
turning your worthless
kingdom into a pile of rubble!
Sounds like she's been
holding that back for a while?
Hey, what do you want to
do with the other one?
Oh the hero?
I've got the perfect idea We plug
her in and use her as a battery.
She has more than enough goddess power.
Battery?
Wait, are you guys talking about...
Now then, Viz, it's time to wreck havoc!
Switch on!
What's going on?
Jinguuji, what's that over there?
Hey, Shen, what is that thing?
Well, it's definitely something.
Now is not the time for jokes.
I get that you're upset, but
no need to bite my head off.
How interesting.
Do you see something, Interrogator?
It's cute. That doesn't help. Oh, sorry.
I meant to say it reminds me of
something I saw in a book long ago.
A creature said to be this
kingdom's guardian deity.
Guardian deity?
You mean those weird forest
animals with the long ears?
Big and intimidating
yet surprisingly cuddly?
And they're fiercely
protective of believers
and their faces can open
up and shoot out light?
If it's designed after one of those
things, then maybe it showed up to help us.
That's what guardian
deities are supposed to do.
It's possible that this
is a lucky omen. Whoa.
Thanks, Guardian Deity.
Actually, based on my experience,
I wouldn't get my hopes up.
Case in point. Okay.
I guess that's a never
mind on the thanks, then.
What is this?
Why would our guardian deity
turn against us? Your majesty?
Can you tell us more about that thing?
It is our kingdom's ancient
defense weapon, Mepon.
A gift bestowed to us by our
goddess in ancient times.
It can melt the enemy's heart
with its adorable design
and melt fortifications with
its enormous beam weapon.
Of course the goddess would make
something so completely asinine.
But the guardian deity can only be activated
by two members of the royal family,
each bearing a holy crest?
How could this be then it has to be
Tachibana and the princess are behind this?
Tachibana so any idea how we take it down?
What makes you think i'd know?
Dang it this thing's got a
lot more kick than i thought!
I'm gonna adjust it a bit!
Don't you dare even think
about adjusting anything!
You already missed the first shot and
messing with it will only make things work!
Quit!
I'm blinding, I'll hit
the next one for sure!
It's powering up again!
Your Majesty, please run!
Jinkuchi, we need to get out of here!
Schwarz, as an adult I can tell you we're
nothing if not complicated creatures.
There's a darkness inside us.
It touches everything, even love.
A handsome face really does
make anything sound believable.
I thought Tachibana was no different.
However, I see now that I was wrong.
The robot might look
embarrassingly stupid,
but it is undoubtedly a vicious
and powerful killing machine.
Tachibana would never unleash
something like that on purpose.
So you're worried about him?
It doesn't matter how I feel.
Whoever's controlling the Guardian deity,
it's my responsibility to stop it.
Well, I'm not going to stand here and
let you take all the glory for yourself.
Are you sure?
You and I are the only ones in the castle
who can do anything against that robot.
If we don't make a stand here and
now, it'll destroy the whole kingdom.
Isn't that what this is?
It's exactly that.
Well, you can take it from here.
Thing is, my supernatural strength
is tied to my proximity to Tachibana,
who isn't here.
So I won't be much help.
Dude, you gotta be kidding me!
You at least have a plan, right?
Something that involves saving
everyone and not leaving me to die?
I'm sorry, but I don't.
What's the matter with you?!
Correct me if I'm wrong, but can't
his sword cut through anything?
So, it stands to reason that it
could also cut through the beam.
That's a good idea, let's go with that.
Can we talk about this first?
A slapped-together plan
cannot be our best option!
If you've got a better one, I'm all ears.
We're kinda out of time to brainstorm.
Good luck. Don't die.
No!
One!
And remember we're all counting on
you to make sure we don't end up dead.
This way please remain calm.
Would you look at that guess it did
work nice you actually did something.
Now I just have to do the same thing
for the next one all right easy peasy.
Because if I don't stop
it then you're gonna
die and I'm gonna die
everyone's gonna die.
You're starting to sound like
a real hero no one asked you.
Congratulations, humans.
You're all still breathing.
Whose voice is that?
Did it come from inside the Watson?
That sounded familiar.
As a reward, I'll share with you my name.
I am this, the incomparably skilled,
top officer for the great Demon Lord.
And when I'm through with you, I'm gonna
take your corpses as soon as you...
Oh, it's her.
If you're one of the Demon Lord's officers,
then there's no need to hold back.
I'm gonna cut you into tiny little pieces!
Really intimidating, Sparts.
You're doing awesome.
You totally got this, buddy.
Can it, both of you!
You talk a lot for a
glorified side character.
It's gonna be fun watching
you eat those words.
Wait, am I losing it or can she
hear us from inside that thing?
I'm guessing it's those stupid ears.
What are you waiting for?
It's not like I've got your precious
hero in here with me or anything.
Oh, wait.
She's using Tachibana as a shield?
Let him go, you dirty cowards!
Now, let's not be so harsh.
How else could she
level the playing field?
She's just a child, after all.
Such a clever plan, too!
Did you come up with it yourself?
Oh, that is it.
Do you want to die for us?
It's so gorgeous.
Why did you have to go
and provoke her like that?
Good.
Next part's on you. Get ready! Wait.
That felt good.
Did I vaporize Four Eyes and his friends?
Of course not!
You missed, you idiot!
Now they're getting away because
of your gross incompetence!
Get your act together and keep firing!
You should've kept blasting from the
beginning instead of trading banter with them!
Mepon isn't built to rapid fire.
It has to cool down for
a while before it can
shoot off another one of
its adorable deathbeds.
That's why have you been
wasting shots this whole time?
Get off my back!
At least I'm trying to keep
them distracted with witty
conversations so they don't
notice we have a weakness.
But when you say witty conversation,
are you talking about the part where you
revealed to them exactly where the hero is?
Did you think that four-eyed barbarian
kept goading you because I was funny?
Quit moaning and stop him before
he's close enough to attack!
Well, if you stop criticizing
me for five seconds,
then maybe I can get back
to trying to kill him!
Get ready to land.
This is all you!
Everything feels broken!
Now that she's lost line of sight,
she'll stop firing on the castle,
giving us a chance to
evacuate the capital?
and leaving an opening to
launch a counterattack.
It seems Mehpon can't fire continuously.
There was a noticeable delay
between the first and second shots.
I suspect that Vizd
attempting all that banter was
her trying to keep us from
noticing its weakness.
But thanks to that, we now know
Tachibana is being kept inside the robot.
We can use this time to close in on it.
My strength will return if we get within
range, and once my power's back, we attack.
Got any questions?
Just one little thing.
Are you okay with me stealing
that got me questions line?
I want to add it to my
list of cool one-liners
to use at some point
during my next adventure.
There's no time for this.
The next shot's coming.
Hey, Jinguji!
I thought maybe a croco-dog would help.
What the?
Why am I floating?
Why even is this place?
Where was I before I woke up here?
They sure love their giant
laser beams in this world.
Am I in the middle of a battle right now?
Jinguji...
Nappan!
Master?
Tsukasa Jinguji,
on behalf of myself and the
school I'm happy to present
you with this award for
your achievements in Kendo.
He's so awesome! I can't
even make the team!
I heard that he can pretty
much do anything he tries.
Man, I wish I was that cool!
This is so stupid!
What idiot can a sword that
can cut through laser beam?
These buildings be
frustratingly effective.
Do we have anything that can counter it?
If I wasn't made for melee combat,
if they close the gap, then
it's basically useless!
Just hit him with whatever power
he used to break me out of jail!
That spell takes more time
than we have to prepare.
Can you do anything right now
besides being a loud mountain man?
My skills are better suited
for covert operations.
We need to figure out
something fast or we're hosed!
If they're able to deflect my next attack,
they'll be dead on top of me
and it's bye-bye bunnybot!
Right,
to keep that from happening, I'll put every
ounce of power we have into this shot!
You fool, that's not a
plan to start to death!
I can't allow it to set up a reaction
too big for Mepoam to get attacked!
Shut up, I know what I'm doing!
Now here I go!
Shut up!
What happened?
Is it busted?
What's going on?
Is everything alright?
The heck?
Everything's shutting
down all of a sudden!
Shutting down? But how? What is this?
We're almost there.
We'll go under it and
attack from the other side.
It won't be able to hit us with that beam.
Look, Jinguji! Above us!
At least you're smart enough to
change up your tactics at close range.
But not smart enough to
take me on, you rotten brat.
Oh, sorry for being a brat!
Tachibana, is that you?
Uh-huh!
I'm cold!
Meifu, it's broken!
I promise it totally wasn't my fault!
It got all dark and scary and
started moving when I found it!
Now I won't even listen!
Someone's going on a rampage!
Rampage?
Is this because I pushed you too hard?
Forgive me, Meifu!
I didn't mean Meifu.
I was referring to the hero.
Huh?!
It's okay, Tachibana.
I'm here to save you!
You'll be safe in there for now.
I'll get you out soon.
Don't worry!
Okay, uh, why would I want out?
I finally got my hands on some real power.
Why should I give it up?
Why go back to the way I was before?
Is it me, or is there
something off with him?
You listen to me, Jinguuji.
I will defeat you! Why?
I came here to save you!
Does it look like I need to be saved?
Then again, you always have to be the hero,
reminding everyone how perfect you are.
Women always adore you,
even though you treat them like
something that crawled out of the sewer!
and bosses love you because you're
perfect at everything you do!
And that's why I friggin'
hate you! Hate you!
Did you see that coming? I did not.
You guys have a fight or something?
No, I thought things were fine between us.
Shut up, Jungle Jim!
You don't understand
what I've gone through!
Maybe you're too perfect
to have repressed emotions,
but I know I'm not for those both of us!
I can feel this power flowing through me,
telling me to crush everything in my path.
For the first time in my
life, I feel invincible!
I didn't realize anyone still
used that kind of cheesy dialogue.
I'm not sure Tachibana would
appreciate hearing that from you.
This is getting out of hand.
Why don't we just bust
in and break him loose?
We're close enough now that your
strength should be back, right?
About that.
In spite of being closer, I'm afraid
my strength still hasn't returned.
What?!
You mean now I have to
fight this thing alone?!
And how exactly do you expect
me to do that, genius?!
All this time, I thought my strength was
tied directly to my proximity to Tachibana.
Huh.
The menu hasn't popped
up to explain anything.
What's going on?
Tachibana, listen to me!
Sure, I'm popular with women and
bosses, but those are separate issues.
Why are you only upset about it now?
Probably because you say stuff like that.
Why?
Oh, I'll tell you why.
You never compliment me!
Huh? Huh?
You have no idea, do you?
How people have treated me just for being
around you, let alone being your friend.
Looking at me like a poo
trailing off a goldfish.
That's barely the tip of the iceberg of
crappy opinions people have had of me!
And you're not any better!
Not one bit! Me?
We've been best friends
almost our entire lives,
and you've never given
me a compliment once!
Even now, I finally managed
to get stronger than you,
and you still haven't said
anything nice about it to me!
You need to do something quick
or he's going to kill us!
I don't know what to do.
He told you straight up that he wanted to
be brave, so just give him a compliment!
Just give a compliment, huh?
That should be easy, right?
Hey, Tachibana! What? What is it?
I think you're super cool, bruh.
You said that because you
feel like you have to!
This is bad!
Shikuchi!
Since Japan has lots of earthquakes,
Japanese doors are built to
take a lot of punishment.
And look, not a scratch.
Never would have thought
to use one like a shield!
Now you've taken it too far!
This isn't a game, Tachibana!
This is dangerous!
If I were anyone else, I'd be—
Well, good thing you're not, huh?
Everyone's always telling you
how amazing and cool you are!
But not me!
They sing your praises and never
say a single kind word about me!
But you're the worst out of all of them!
It's like you can't find a
single good thing about me!
and that hurts!
I just want a tenth of the
positive attention you get.
I'm sorry you feel that way,
and I'm trying to understand,
but I can't do it when
you're throwing a tantrum!
Shut up!
Don't you think I know that already?
I'd find some better way
to do this if I could.
I understand that I'm being
childish and self-centered,
and I realize it's not right, but sometimes
I don't know how to be a grown-up.
I'm not smart.
I'm not attractive.
I always need saving.
There's nothing special about me!
He really is hurting.
That's why they called me
a trailing goldfish poo!
Because they knew I could
never be what you are, Jinguji!
So no matter how much
cuter or stronger I get,
if I'm worthless to you, it
means I truly am nothing!
This is what it always comes back to!
The only thing in my life I can brag
about is having you for a best friend!
And I'm sick of being someone
who has something that's wrong!
Let's go!
Fabulous!
Yeah!
I will now read a letter.
I have a question about that freaky
weird dog crocodile creature.
Oh, you mean the Crocodog?
Do you know what kind of sound it makes?
Let's find out!
Come on, make a sound for the audience!
Come on, speak, speak!